<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jung on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/jung/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jung on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 20:36:30 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/jung/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>When Meditation Makes Things Worse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2021/02/20/when-meditation-makes-things-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 20:36:30 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2021/02/20/when-meditation-makes-things-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One does not become enlightened by imagining figures of light, but by making the darkness conscious.&amp;rdquo; ― C. G. Jung&#xA;Some practitioners of meditation appear to be holding on to assumptions which, while possibly beneficial in the proper context, can in fact end up being actually harmful when misunderstood. I speak from personal experience here, and also often see others struggling with this. You may well recognise it from your own practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Life Really Predetermined?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2021/01/13/is-your-life-really-predetermined/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 22:20:30 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2021/01/13/is-your-life-really-predetermined/</guid>
      <description>I was watching, and enjoying, the series Devs, developed by Alex Garland - if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, it&amp;rsquo;s a philosophical conundrum wrapped in a streaming mini-series format, something like Black Mirror or Mr Robot, with a very nice aesthetic to the music and design. Or it&amp;rsquo;s a standard sci-fi mini-series with pretensions to having something to say philosophically. Anyway it got me thinking, which presumably is the point.&#xA;Back in the day I was somewhat into teachers like Ramesh Balsekar, Roger Castillo, Tony Parsons and Lisa Cairns, who all basically go with the idea of a totally predetermined universe - Wikipedia explains: Ramesh Balsekar - Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema As Koan Part 3: The Way Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/08/24/eczema-as-koan-part-3-the-way-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/08/24/eczema-as-koan-part-3-the-way-out/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of my account of how I came to experience full healing from a very severe experience of eczema lasting several years. Part one is here and part two is here.&#xA;3I have covered my journey of healing and discovery up until this point, which took the form of a voyage into the depths of Hell and out again.&#xA;Looking back now, I can see that – after all the very difficult experiences of reliving my own birth, and releasing so much anger and resentment (I have barely scratched the surface here), plus experiencing mythic situations both hellish and heavenly – the real breakthrough came during the sixth session of Holotropic Breathwork I experienced in Barcelona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema as Koan Part 2: The Descent Into Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/08/16/eczema-as-koan-part-2-the-descent-into-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2014 19:19:10 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/08/16/eczema-as-koan-part-2-the-descent-into-hell/</guid>
      <description>This is part two of my account of how I came to experience full healing from a very severe experience of eczema lasting several years. Part one is here and part three is here&#xA;Having ‘turned the corner’ as it were, (in terms of hope for the future if not in an actual improvement in my health), although I didn’t know for sure then if it was a genuine ‘touching rock bottom’, or merely one more step on the way down, I began to search for something which might genuinely make a difference to my health.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
