<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Love on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:43123/tags/love/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Love on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:43123/tags/love/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Myth of Progress and the Fear of Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2020/03/20/myth-of-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:44:27 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2020/03/20/myth-of-progress/</guid>
      <description>have you seen the moon tonight it&#39;s very nearly full so eat and drink your fill for soon &#39;twill come to pass the king will feed the grass and sacrifice his personality to the tree to the sea cos &#39;it&#39;s not me&#39; oh no personality will never pass for me because I&#39;m really the grass - Daevid Allen, Song of Satisfaction, from the album &#39;Good Morning&#39;, 1975. All contemporary political movements are in some way progressive, and in this article I will argue where that comes from, and why buying into the idea of Progress, as currently understood, will only serve to deepen our current predicament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Code is Love”: Justice On the Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2018/05/16/code-is-love-justice-on-the-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2018/05/16/code-is-love-justice-on-the-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>We all know that ‘love’ is a dirty word these days. It is relentlessly abused by advertisers who always seek to exploit our earliest psychological bonds with our parents and then by sheer repetition, associate themselves with those symbols we learnt in our childhood relating to those bonds. ‘Love’ is one such, and massively overused by Hollywood to boot, in its romantic aspect.&#xA;However, as Cornel West so eloquently put it —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Bottom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/05/rock-bottom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/05/rock-bottom/</guid>
      <description>The recent article by Josh Ellis ‘Everyone I Know Is Brokenhearted which has apparently gone viral, seems to have struck a chord among large numbers of people seriously disaffected by the current state of affairs in which we find ourselves. I also read a moving companion piece in A counterpoint for the brokenhearted in which the author provides pays tribute to a friend who did everything he could to relieve the suffering of desperate people.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
