<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alchemy on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/alchemy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alchemy on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:47:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/alchemy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Check out the Alquimystica Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/06/alquimystica-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:47:18 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2023/05/06/alquimystica-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Not enough content and information in your life? Ok yes I know you are drowning in it, as are we all. But if you are interested in the very specific topic of psychedelic integration and how to bring the insights of your entheogenic adventures into your daily life, then I think you will be interested in this particular episode, featuring an interview between my friend Emer and Marc Aixalà, the author of Psychotherapy for Non-Ordinary States of Consciousness and a founder member of ICEERS (The International Center for Ethnobotanical Education, Research, and Service).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema As Koan Part 3: The Way Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2014/08/24/eczema-as-koan-part-3-the-way-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2014/08/24/eczema-as-koan-part-3-the-way-out/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of my account of how I came to experience full healing from a very severe experience of eczema lasting several years. Part one is here and part two is here.&#xA;3I have covered my journey of healing and discovery up until this point, which took the form of a voyage into the depths of Hell and out again.&#xA;Looking back now, I can see that – after all the very difficult experiences of reliving my own birth, and releasing so much anger and resentment (I have barely scratched the surface here), plus experiencing mythic situations both hellish and heavenly – the real breakthrough came during the sixth session of Holotropic Breathwork I experienced in Barcelona.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
