<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Philosophy on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:43123/tags/philosophy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Philosophy on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 11:47:18 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:43123/tags/philosophy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Spreadsheet Brain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2023/09/25/spreadsheet-brain/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 11:47:18 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2023/09/25/spreadsheet-brain/</guid>
      <description>“The inability to conceive of its own devastation will tend to be the blind spot of any culture.&amp;quot; — Jonathan Lear in Radical Hope: Ethics in the Face of Cultural Devastation.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;What is soul? I don&amp;rsquo;t know&#xA;Soul is the ring around your bathtub&amp;rdquo; — Funkadelic, What Is Soul?&#xA;(meme courtesy of Ashley Colby)&#xA;Ashley Colby, a US citizen, resides in Uruguay, lives a &amp;lsquo;Little House on the Pampa&amp;rsquo; trad-wife lifestyle (it&amp;rsquo;s not LARPing if you do it for real), and crucially for this essay, is the coiner of the term &amp;lsquo;spreadsheet brain&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Check out the Alquimystica Podcast</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2023/05/06/alquimystica-podcast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 11:47:18 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2023/05/06/alquimystica-podcast/</guid>
      <description>Not enough content and information in your life? Ok yes I know you are drowning in it, as are we all. But if you are interested in the very specific topic of psychedelic integration and how to bring the insights of your entheogenic adventures into your daily life, then I think you will be interested in this particular episode, featuring an interview between my friend Emer and Marc Aixalà, the author of Psychotherapy for Non-Ordinary States of Consciousness and a founder member of ICEERS (The International Center for Ethnobotanical Education, Research, and Service).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Mind Is Buddha Mind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/ordinary-mind-is-buddha-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 15:11:11 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/ordinary-mind-is-buddha-mind/</guid>
      <description>There is a zen saying: &amp;ldquo;ordinary mind is Buddha mind&amp;rdquo;. I did understand this saying, but yesterday I realised it in a whole new way: Often what prompts us to start investigating &amp;rsquo;this spiritual stuff&amp;rsquo;, is a feeling of isolation; we feel as if, as this quote from A.E. Housman illustrates —&#xA;&amp;lsquo;I, a stranger and afraid, in a world I never made.&amp;rsquo;&#xA;We feel cut off from the source of life in some undefinable way, atomised by societal conditioning and our own past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Meditation Makes Things Worse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/when-meditation-makes-things-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 20:36:30 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/when-meditation-makes-things-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One does not become enlightened by imagining figures of light, but by making the darkness conscious.&amp;rdquo; ― C. G. Jung&#xA;Some practitioners of meditation appear to be holding on to assumptions which, while possibly beneficial in the proper context, can in fact end up being actually harmful when misunderstood. I speak from personal experience here, and also often see others struggling with this. You may well recognise it from your own practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Life Really Predetermined?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2021/01/13/is-your-life-really-predetermined/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 22:20:30 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2021/01/13/is-your-life-really-predetermined/</guid>
      <description>I was watching, and enjoying, the series Devs, developed by Alex Garland - if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, it&amp;rsquo;s a philosophical conundrum wrapped in a streaming mini-series format, something like Black Mirror or Mr Robot, with a very nice aesthetic to the music and design. Or it&amp;rsquo;s a standard sci-fi mini-series with pretensions to having something to say philosophically. Anyway it got me thinking, which presumably is the point.&#xA;Back in the day I was somewhat into teachers like Ramesh Balsekar, Roger Castillo, Tony Parsons and Lisa Cairns, who all basically go with the idea of a totally predetermined universe - Wikipedia explains: Ramesh Balsekar - Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colliding Utopias… and John Lennon’s ‘Imagine’</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2009/06/06/colliding-utopias-and-john-lennons-imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2009 14:41:43 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2009/06/06/colliding-utopias-and-john-lennons-imagine/</guid>
      <description>Last night I had the realisation, but to be honest it felt like a revelation, (and like all good revelations I can’t now understand why it wasn’t already obvious to me), that a great deal of the conflict in the world is caused by clashes between different groups trying to promote their own version of ‘utopia’. I had vaguely intimated this on being sent an article on John Gray, a distinctly anti-utopian philosopher, by my friend Nils Borg.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
