<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Non-Duality on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:43123/tags/non-duality/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Non-Duality on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 15:11:11 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:43123/tags/non-duality/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ordinary Mind Is Buddha Mind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/ordinary-mind-is-buddha-mind/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 15:11:11 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/ordinary-mind-is-buddha-mind/</guid>
      <description>There is a zen saying: &amp;ldquo;ordinary mind is Buddha mind&amp;rdquo;. I did understand this saying, but yesterday I realised it in a whole new way: Often what prompts us to start investigating &amp;rsquo;this spiritual stuff&amp;rsquo;, is a feeling of isolation; we feel as if, as this quote from A.E. Housman illustrates —&#xA;&amp;lsquo;I, a stranger and afraid, in a world I never made.&amp;rsquo;&#xA;We feel cut off from the source of life in some undefinable way, atomised by societal conditioning and our own past.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>When Meditation Makes Things Worse</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/when-meditation-makes-things-worse/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Feb 2021 20:36:30 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2021/02/20/when-meditation-makes-things-worse/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ldquo;One does not become enlightened by imagining figures of light, but by making the darkness conscious.&amp;rdquo; ― C. G. Jung&#xA;Some practitioners of meditation appear to be holding on to assumptions which, while possibly beneficial in the proper context, can in fact end up being actually harmful when misunderstood. I speak from personal experience here, and also often see others struggling with this. You may well recognise it from your own practice.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Is Your Life Really Predetermined?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2021/01/13/is-your-life-really-predetermined/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 22:20:30 +0200</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2021/01/13/is-your-life-really-predetermined/</guid>
      <description>I was watching, and enjoying, the series Devs, developed by Alex Garland - if you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen it, it&amp;rsquo;s a philosophical conundrum wrapped in a streaming mini-series format, something like Black Mirror or Mr Robot, with a very nice aesthetic to the music and design. Or it&amp;rsquo;s a standard sci-fi mini-series with pretensions to having something to say philosophically. Anyway it got me thinking, which presumably is the point.&#xA;Back in the day I was somewhat into teachers like Ramesh Balsekar, Roger Castillo, Tony Parsons and Lisa Cairns, who all basically go with the idea of a totally predetermined universe - Wikipedia explains: Ramesh Balsekar - Wikipedia</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Brother is the Reincarnation of God</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/08/03/big-brother-is-the-reincarnation-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 10:40:44 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/08/03/big-brother-is-the-reincarnation-of-god/</guid>
      <description>‘God is dead. God remains dead. And we have killed him. Yet his shadow still looms.’ — Nietzsche, The Gay Science.&#xA;‘In one period of experimentation with acid, Barrett and another friend, Paul Charrier, end up naked in the bath, reciting: “No rules, no rules”.’ – Manning, Toby (2006). The Rough Guide to Pink Floyd.&#xA;Taken from Boing Boing&#xA;Ok here we go… I had a dream last night – I was in a large, old-fashioned wood-panelled library; on the wall was a painting of a mischievous looking wizard – in appearance something like a cross between Alan Watts and Gandalf as played by Sir Ian McKellen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Question?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/06/23/a-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 14:04:57 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/06/23/a-question/</guid>
      <description>Swift easy despair&#xA;Tempt me to the edge&#xA;A senseless swoon&#xA;Black eyes point&#xA;Back to the womb&#xA;A narrative spent-&#xA;The infant only has moments,&#xA;No breeze of story&#xA;Catches his sails.&#xA;He twists in the winds of hazard,&#xA;Careless, not free&#xA;Because freedom is owned by its opposite&#xA;As all things&#xA;Extracted from the fabric&#xA;Like time&#xA;A conception laid bare&#xA;Shown to be without foundation&#xA;We fall</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
