<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Privacy on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/privacy/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Privacy on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 19:50:14 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/privacy/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Privacy, Responsibility, and ‘Floating Anarchy’</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/2013/10/20/privacy-responsibility-and-floating-anarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 19:50:14 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/2013/10/20/privacy-responsibility-and-floating-anarchy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://2018.guyjames.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/tigredebengala-300x198.jpg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;Tigre-de-bengala&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If national life becomes so perfect as to become self-regulated, no representation become necessary. There is then a state of enlightened anarchy. In such a state everyone is his own ruler. He rules himself in such a manner that he is never a hindrance to his neighbour. In the ideal State, therefore, there is no political power because there is no State.’&lt;/strong&gt; – Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;‘&lt;strong&gt;Anarchy is not misrule but no rule’&lt;/strong&gt; – Floating Anarchy Manifesto, Daevid Allen&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Following on from my previous post, ‘&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:1313/2013/08/03/big-brother-is-the-reincarnation-of-god/&#34; &#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;&gt;Big Brother is the Reincarnation of God&lt;/a&gt;, I have been considering how we give up our power to our god-surrogate, whether that be in the form of governments, corporations, or indeed organised religions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course one of the main ways in which we surrender ourselves to the ‘Man Upstairs’ is through opting for convenience over our own long term benefit. I remember when Google first launched the GMail service, and certain troublemakers pointed out that the Big G would have to analyse all our private emails in order to supply us with targeted advertising. I considered these warnings for a few minutes, to be sure, but then remembering the Google motto of ‘Don’t Be Evil’, and their perceived track record of generally being pretty good around privacy issues, I chose, as apparently a vast majority did, to ignore the potential dangers and focus on the features of this new email service. And I have to say, that GMail &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a great email service, and certainly pushed the whole notion of how to provide email up a level, introducing many innovations which have since been copied by other providers (even Microsoft eventually caught on, after a few years).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But with the Snowden revelations, and those of other whistleblowers, we realise that our trust in Google was misplaced, or perhaps being more charitable, our trust in how the internet works was misplaced – we still don’t know how much Google or other corporations knew about, or are able to prevent, the likes of the NSA spying on everyone’s emails. We may assume that as they didn’t see it as a problem to analyse everyone’s emails themselves, that personal privacy was not exactly at the top of their list, but of course we had the clear option of rejecting the GMail model on privacy grounds, and we chose not to, which brings me to one of the main points of this article.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
