<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Thoughts on Guy James</title>
    <link>http://localhost:43123/categories/thoughts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Thoughts on Guy James</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <managingEditor>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</webMaster>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:44:27 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:43123/categories/thoughts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Myth of Progress and the Fear of Death</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2020/03/20/myth-of-progress/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 18:44:27 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2020/03/20/myth-of-progress/</guid>
      <description>have you seen the moon tonight it&#39;s very nearly full so eat and drink your fill for soon &#39;twill come to pass the king will feed the grass and sacrifice his personality to the tree to the sea cos &#39;it&#39;s not me&#39; oh no personality will never pass for me because I&#39;m really the grass - Daevid Allen, Song of Satisfaction, from the album &#39;Good Morning&#39;, 1975. All contemporary political movements are in some way progressive, and in this article I will argue where that comes from, and why buying into the idea of Progress, as currently understood, will only serve to deepen our current predicament.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>“Code is Love”: Justice On the Blockchain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2018/05/16/code-is-love-justice-on-the-blockchain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 May 2018 15:01:27 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2018/05/16/code-is-love-justice-on-the-blockchain/</guid>
      <description>We all know that ‘love’ is a dirty word these days. It is relentlessly abused by advertisers who always seek to exploit our earliest psychological bonds with our parents and then by sheer repetition, associate themselves with those symbols we learnt in our childhood relating to those bonds. ‘Love’ is one such, and massively overused by Hollywood to boot, in its romantic aspect.&#xA;However, as Cornel West so eloquently put it —</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Here Be Dragons!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2016/10/04/here-be-dragons/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Oct 2016 10:39:54 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2016/10/04/here-be-dragons/</guid>
      <description>Manifesto For A New Adventure “Those who do not move, do not notice their chains.“ – Rosa Luxemburg&#xA;“Don’t get caught up in the spectacle of opposition. Oppose the spectacle.” “Those who lack imagination cannot imagine what is lacking.” – Situationist graffiti&#xA;“When an inner situation is not made conscious, it appears outside as fate”. – C. G. Jung&#xA;“Why should you study and practice Magick? Because you can’t help doing it, and you had better do it well than badly.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema As Koan Update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2016/01/09/eczema-as-koan-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2016 10:22:56 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2016/01/09/eczema-as-koan-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I thought I would add a brief update related to my &lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:43123/2014/08/12/eczema-as-koan-part-1/&#34; &#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;&gt;previous posts&lt;/a&gt; about becoming healed from severe eczema. These passages are adapted from replies to people on the Eczema/Topical Steroid Withdrawal group on Facebook. Given the ephemeral nature of Facebook I wanted to save them somewhere in case they might be useful to anyone in the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Emptiness of ‘Emptiness’:  P2P Spiritual Knowledge and Community</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2014/11/30/the-emptiness-of-emptiness-p2p-spiritual-knowledge-and-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Nov 2014 18:40:29 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2014/11/30/the-emptiness-of-emptiness-p2p-spiritual-knowledge-and-community/</guid>
      <description>Michel Bauwens points out in his article ‘If we can have p2p economics, why not p2p spirituality?’ that the dominant spiritual and economic models of a particular age often mirror each other:&#xA;“Spirituality and religion always bear the hallmark of the social structures in which they were born and become embedded. Emerging religions often represent a partial transformation of these social structures because they represent new forms of consciousness, but they can never become hegemonic if they are not rooted in, and accepted by, the mainstream social logic.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema As Koan Part 3: The Way Out</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/24/eczema-as-koan-part-3-the-way-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Aug 2014 11:38:57 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/24/eczema-as-koan-part-3-the-way-out/</guid>
      <description>This is part three of my account of how I came to experience full healing from a very severe experience of eczema lasting several years. Part one is here and part two is here.&#xA;3I have covered my journey of healing and discovery up until this point, which took the form of a voyage into the depths of Hell and out again.&#xA;Looking back now, I can see that – after all the very difficult experiences of reliving my own birth, and releasing so much anger and resentment (I have barely scratched the surface here), plus experiencing mythic situations both hellish and heavenly – the real breakthrough came during the sixth session of Holotropic Breathwork I experienced in Barcelona.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema as Koan Part 2: The Descent Into Hell</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/16/eczema-as-koan-part-2-the-descent-into-hell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2014 19:19:10 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/16/eczema-as-koan-part-2-the-descent-into-hell/</guid>
      <description>This is part two of my account of how I came to experience full healing from a very severe experience of eczema lasting several years. Part one is here and part three is here&#xA;Having ‘turned the corner’ as it were, (in terms of hope for the future if not in an actual improvement in my health), although I didn’t know for sure then if it was a genuine ‘touching rock bottom’, or merely one more step on the way down, I began to search for something which might genuinely make a difference to my health.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eczema as Koan Part 1</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/12/eczema-as-koan-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2014 18:51:03 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/12/eczema-as-koan-part-1/</guid>
      <description>This is part one of a three part article; part two is here and the final part is here&#xA;An excerpt from a recent article on my blog:&#xA;“About four years ago I spilt up with my girlfriend and subsequently became rather ill – I was eventually hospitalised and on admission the first nurse who saw me in a hospital gown assumed I had been burnt in a house fire, so badly destroyed was the weeping, bleeding skin all over my body.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Rock Bottom</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/05/rock-bottom/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Aug 2014 21:08:58 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2014/08/05/rock-bottom/</guid>
      <description>The recent article by Josh Ellis ‘Everyone I Know Is Brokenhearted which has apparently gone viral, seems to have struck a chord among large numbers of people seriously disaffected by the current state of affairs in which we find ourselves. I also read a moving companion piece in A counterpoint for the brokenhearted in which the author provides pays tribute to a friend who did everything he could to relieve the suffering of desperate people.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Privacy, Responsibility, and ‘Floating Anarchy’</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/10/20/privacy-responsibility-and-floating-anarchy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2013 19:50:14 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/10/20/privacy-responsibility-and-floating-anarchy/</guid>
      <description>&lt;figure&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://2018.guyjames.com/wp-content/uploads/2013/10/tigredebengala-300x198.jpg&#34;&#xA;    alt=&#34;Tigre-de-bengala&#34;&gt;&#xA;&lt;/figure&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If national life becomes so perfect as to become self-regulated, no representation become necessary. There is then a state of enlightened anarchy. In such a state everyone is his own ruler. He rules himself in such a manner that he is never a hindrance to his neighbour. In the ideal State, therefore, there is no political power because there is no State.’&lt;/strong&gt; – Gandhi&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;‘&lt;strong&gt;Anarchy is not misrule but no rule’&lt;/strong&gt; – Floating Anarchy Manifesto, Daevid Allen&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Following on from my previous post, ‘&lt;a href=&#34;http://localhost:43123/2013/08/03/big-brother-is-the-reincarnation-of-god/&#34; &#xA;  &#xA;  &#xA;&gt;Big Brother is the Reincarnation of God&lt;/a&gt;, I have been considering how we give up our power to our god-surrogate, whether that be in the form of governments, corporations, or indeed organised religions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Of course one of the main ways in which we surrender ourselves to the ‘Man Upstairs’ is through opting for convenience over our own long term benefit. I remember when Google first launched the GMail service, and certain troublemakers pointed out that the Big G would have to analyse all our private emails in order to supply us with targeted advertising. I considered these warnings for a few minutes, to be sure, but then remembering the Google motto of ‘Don’t Be Evil’, and their perceived track record of generally being pretty good around privacy issues, I chose, as apparently a vast majority did, to ignore the potential dangers and focus on the features of this new email service. And I have to say, that GMail &lt;em&gt;is&lt;/em&gt; a great email service, and certainly pushed the whole notion of how to provide email up a level, introducing many innovations which have since been copied by other providers (even Microsoft eventually caught on, after a few years).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But with the Snowden revelations, and those of other whistleblowers, we realise that our trust in Google was misplaced, or perhaps being more charitable, our trust in how the internet works was misplaced – we still don’t know how much Google or other corporations knew about, or are able to prevent, the likes of the NSA spying on everyone’s emails. We may assume that as they didn’t see it as a problem to analyse everyone’s emails themselves, that personal privacy was not exactly at the top of their list, but of course we had the clear option of rejecting the GMail model on privacy grounds, and we chose not to, which brings me to one of the main points of this article.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Big Brother is the Reincarnation of God</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/08/03/big-brother-is-the-reincarnation-of-god/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2013 10:40:44 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/08/03/big-brother-is-the-reincarnation-of-god/</guid>
      <description>‘God is dead. God remains dead. And we have killed him. Yet his shadow still looms.’ — Nietzsche, The Gay Science.&#xA;‘In one period of experimentation with acid, Barrett and another friend, Paul Charrier, end up naked in the bath, reciting: “No rules, no rules”.’ – Manning, Toby (2006). The Rough Guide to Pink Floyd.&#xA;Taken from Boing Boing&#xA;Ok here we go… I had a dream last night – I was in a large, old-fashioned wood-panelled library; on the wall was a painting of a mischievous looking wizard – in appearance something like a cross between Alan Watts and Gandalf as played by Sir Ian McKellen.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Question?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/06/23/a-question/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2013 14:04:57 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/06/23/a-question/</guid>
      <description>Swift easy despair&#xA;Tempt me to the edge&#xA;A senseless swoon&#xA;Black eyes point&#xA;Back to the womb&#xA;A narrative spent-&#xA;The infant only has moments,&#xA;No breeze of story&#xA;Catches his sails.&#xA;He twists in the winds of hazard,&#xA;Careless, not free&#xA;Because freedom is owned by its opposite&#xA;As all things&#xA;Extracted from the fabric&#xA;Like time&#xA;A conception laid bare&#xA;Shown to be without foundation&#xA;We fall</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ananta</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/05/15/ananta/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2013 21:13:34 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/05/15/ananta/</guid>
      <description>The endless sweep of the horizon&#xA;From my window seat, the sea&#xA;Gazing past the concrete holiday boxes&#xA;Today the wind is fierce&#xA;A hulk with two cranes shelters distantly in the bay&#xA;Overpowering banks of light trained on the shore&#xA;Pin points as&#xA;The sun sinks into the grey beyond&#xA;The steel sides groan against the waves&#xA;Its lights now become the sun&#xA;We can only know the endless by that which seems to end</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get A Job</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2013/01/22/get-a-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Jan 2013 15:31:23 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2013/01/22/get-a-job/</guid>
      <description>I wrote this article at the height of the ‘Occupy’ protests around the world – for some reason I never posted it – the other day I found it and I believe the majority of it is still relevant some months down the line, so here it is:&#xA;The end of drudgery and the start of doing some real work.&#xA;When I was in my early 20s, and searching around in some kind of depressed fug for ‘a job’, I had a memorable dream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning Is Nigh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2011/10/09/beginning-is-nigh/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Oct 2011 18:12:38 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2011/10/09/beginning-is-nigh/</guid>
      <description>Having read Douglas Rushkoff’s excellent appraisal of the Occupy Wall Street movement, I felt I would like to add some thoughts.&#xA;There is a new consciousness crystallising, and Rushkoff said something which (as usual) was very insightful, in that the mainstream media are having trouble getting to grips with the (r)evolution because they can’t see it, it just looks like a jumble of different causes all mixed together, and the people at the heart of it refuse to discuss it on the mainstream media’s terms, and reduce everything to black and white and soundbites.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kill Your Practice</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2011/07/01/kill-your-practice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 14:53:42 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2011/07/01/kill-your-practice/</guid>
      <description>Buddhists call what they do when they sit down to meditate ‘practice’. Of course all words are imperfect when we enter the tricky realm of the non-dual but I really feel this term is misleading if we are wanting to enter the Absolute in our meditation. The idea of meditation being something one practices and gradually becomes good at creates the feeling that in the future, when we are ‘good at meditation’ we will enter the Eternal Present.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Humility</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2011/06/12/humility/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2011 15:06:40 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2011/06/12/humility/</guid>
      <description>Be thankful for your imperfect human body, because if our bodies were as beautiful as our soul, we would be insufferably conceited.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Just BEING is a Revolutionary Act</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2011/05/26/just-being-is-a-revolutionary-act/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 May 2011 10:54:29 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2011/05/26/just-being-is-a-revolutionary-act/</guid>
      <description>By which I mean, just ‘being’ without doing anything, thinking anything in particular, or trying to be anyone special.&#xA;In this way we are not ‘productive’, we are not caught in the trap of ‘becoming’, we are not placing hope in an illusory ‘future’ which acts as a drug to stop us seeing the reality of how things are right now.&#xA;We are defying the corporate mindset that all people have to be efficient cogs in the machine, the machine which will deliver us to our inevitable technological Utopia.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Resonance of Place</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2011/04/09/resonance-of-place/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2011 13:57:55 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2011/04/09/resonance-of-place/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;How much does location play a part in your sound?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;“I am fascinated by the resonance certain places can have, which invests them with almost heroic proportions. The very name of a place itself can inspire awe and credibility. There are countless examples of this in American folk and pop music and beyond and I am trying to key into a mode which elevates places around Britain, which have a personal resonance, into the realm of myth and mystery. In this sense certain locations play a big part in the music we make; trying to mythologise a place which provided the backdrop to some great personal realisation or other.”&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;–&lt;em&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;http://www.theskinny.co.uk/music/interviews/trembling-bells-alex-neilson-i-d-probably-be-a-professional-footballer-if-it-wasn-t-for-trout-mask-replica&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;Alex Neilson, Trembling Bells&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>This is the News</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2010/11/07/this-is-the-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 10:43:12 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2010/11/07/this-is-the-news/</guid>
      <description>I just realised what &amp;lsquo;The News&amp;rsquo; is; it is not primarily a record of the day’s most important events but is actually a presentation of a point of view about a single subject. That subject is Death and the opinion you are invited to have is that it is a Bad Thing. Look at the grim faces of the newsreaders as they describe how many have perished and in what way.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Music of the Sun: The Eternal Fascination of Yes!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2009/09/30/music-of-the-sun-the-eternal-fascination-of-yes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2009 21:26:53 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2009/09/30/music-of-the-sun-the-eternal-fascination-of-yes/</guid>
      <description>Prog rock. Progressive Rock. Filthy, hated, heretical noise, utterly shunned since Year Zero (1976). But I love it… or a great deal of it anyway.&#xA;Those who lump dazzling avatars of God’s Own Progression like Yes, Genesis (the early version, naturally) and King Crimson in with lumpen regurgitators of egoistic bombast like Emerson Lake and Palmer are merely demonstrating their own cloth-ears. Where ELP sound totally of their time, Yes in particular are still in the fantastic future world they created for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You the One?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2009/06/14/are-you-the-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Jun 2009 21:13:59 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2009/06/14/are-you-the-one/</guid>
      <description>I was just thinking about the concept of ‘the One’ in relationships and how it affects our expectations. People fall in love and in the midst of the euphoria of those initial weeks (or months if they’re lucky) of bliss, they often believe they have found ‘the One’ – whether they already believed they were waiting for such a person, or the intensity of the experience leads them to believe in such an ideal relationship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colliding Utopias… and John Lennon’s ‘Imagine’</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2009/06/06/colliding-utopias-and-john-lennons-imagine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2009 14:41:43 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2009/06/06/colliding-utopias-and-john-lennons-imagine/</guid>
      <description>Last night I had the realisation, but to be honest it felt like a revelation, (and like all good revelations I can’t now understand why it wasn’t already obvious to me), that a great deal of the conflict in the world is caused by clashes between different groups trying to promote their own version of ‘utopia’. I had vaguely intimated this on being sent an article on John Gray, a distinctly anti-utopian philosopher, by my friend Nils Borg.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Bubble Burst</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2008/09/30/the-bubble-burst/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2008 22:00:56 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2008/09/30/the-bubble-burst/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been hearing a lot about the Stock Market bubble bursting, or the financial bubble has burst or whatever, but what it really seems to be is that the whole bubble of our culture is about to burst.&#xA;And why? For the same reason that these big financial institutions are in trouble: when something gets totally cut off from reality, it forms a bubble, and forms a little reality of its own- the trouble is, this reality, like any bubble, will pop sooner or later.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Herzog’s ‘Heart of Glass’</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2008/07/28/thoughts-on-herzogs-heart-of-glass/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2008 16:35:22 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2008/07/28/thoughts-on-herzogs-heart-of-glass/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I just saw this film yesterday and it totally blew me away. Someone had said I should see it but I couldn’t remember why, I watched the whole thing with this nagging feeling at the back of my mind that there was something very odd about it.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;After it was over I looked it up on the net and then I remembered: the reason I particularly wanted to see it (apart from the fact that I want to see all of Herzog’s films), and  &lt;span class=&#34;pullquote&#34;&gt;one of the reasons it is very odd, is that all the actors in it are hypnotised, except one&lt;/span&gt;, Josef Bierbichler, who plays Hias, the herdsman who can see into the future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Living in a World Without Trends</title>
      <link>http://localhost:43123/2008/06/30/living-in-a-world-without-trends/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jun 2008 09:46:24 +0000</pubDate><author>info@guyjames.com (Guy James)</author>
      <guid>http://localhost:43123/2008/06/30/living-in-a-world-without-trends/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I’ve just realised something that may have been obvious to everyone else for ages: that now the vice-like grip of major label record labels has been loosened, the music business has more or less reached the end of trends.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
